The wave that flows to the aluminization can be fast
sound can be curved
Thank you for watching!
In the world we live in, there is another world, a parallel world.
Normally, this world and ours do not intersect.
But I never thought this would happen because of Sasai.
Oh, I forgot to introduce myself.
My name is Lina.
I'm in a band called Crown's End.
Well, we've only been together for 3 months.
But the truth is, I've always had a dream.
What? A table tennis player?
What? Tap dancer?
What's next, a tower tennis player?
No, no, no.
My dream is to be an idol.
I want to wear a skirt that flutters like a butterfly,
I want to be an idol who can make everyone happy in a sparkling outfit.
You want me to start already?
I know, I know.
Don't miss this story of my experience.
High in the sky, I see the light
I'll look at you and you at me and we'll run
I'll overflow with your smile, my feelings
I've got feelings for you, but it's the best day of my life with you
Sexy Queen The beginning The answer points
We're here
Be ready Aiming for tomorrow
Now, me and me, we're gonna give it our all
Subtitle Kiminomiya
at time
I'll wake you up, all over the world
Next, I'll draw a dream that will never end
You're our first
Take my hand, let's go over, step by step
Let's go with all our might
♪ We made a promise to each other ♪ ♪ Without making a promise ♪
Let's change it into a day that will never end
And I'll change it on the day that never ends
Ride the wind, spilling away, one more step, to the dream of heaven and earth
Dance, dance, dance, we dance, we dance
We're dancing, we're dancing, we're dancing, we're dancing, we're dancing, we're dancing
Come on, let us go on and on and on to heaven
Oh!
Thank you for coming to the end of the cloud today and for coming to our 3 month anniversary performance!
Thank you.
Let's all enjoy the show until the end!
Next up is Rina's song.
Enjoy the show until the end, everyone!
Bye bye!
Now, I'd like you to listen to this song.
Please listen to it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, squeejer
me
belovend е
What a cute outfit!
Rina, it's already starting!
It's Crapo's solo show today!
Let's make everyone fall in love with us!
Crapo? Idol?
I think I know what it is.
Stop messing around and let's get ready.
May my right hand be in your pocket.
In your pocket.
I hope the winter sky
See, it's snowing again this year
I'll give you a hug
Hold on to these feelings
See, my heart is so clear, my love is so clear, it's almost there
I'll hold on to the feelings I've closed up to you again and again
I'm trembling, I love you so much, I'm trembling, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much
Singing voice echoing
Wow, magic, spinning a letter
Almond rings of emptiness
Endlessly, your dreams
Still shining, still pointing forward
I'm still dreaming
If it's a dream, I want to know you, I'll call the light
Idols are so much fun!
It was so beautiful with the penlights all over the place
I wish I could sing more
If I do sing, what should I sing next?
I'll sing a ballad or something...?
No, no, no, no, no, but there are also some gay songs...
What should I do?
I'm getting sleepy...
Sigh, mmmm mmmm mmmm mmmm mmmm mmmm mmmm
Leena! Leena! Wake up! We're live!
What are you sleeping already?
Rina's solo song is next!
1. album album album album album album album album album album album album album album album album album album album album Albums Albums Albums Albums Albums Albums Albums Albums Albums Albums
Albums!
Hey, hey, that thing...
I mean, the butterfly was the trigger that sent us to the parallel universe.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But it's good to be back in the real world, isn't it?
I thought if I found that butterfly, I could go to the parallel universe too.
But you said it couldn't happen in real life.
huh?
But... but... don't you really want to go there?
Yeah.Yeah. - Yeah.
I'd like to go there the most.
I guess.
Because it's a dream world.
There you go.
See?
I want to go there too.
If I go to a parallel world, can I be an idol too?
What?
If I went to a parallel world, would I be able to be an idol, too?
Oh, sure.
Yes, I'm sure.
Parallel.
But...
I can't see half of it, and you can't see the other half.
Yeah.
If I could... if I could go...
Wouldn't you like to go there? A parallel universe.
Yeah. - Yeah.
You were talking about that earlier.
You'd like to go there, wouldn't you?
Yeah, I'd love to.
Sorry, I was too busy eating popcorn to listen.
I see.
I wonder if he's around here.
If there's a movie, we'll all go looking for him.
Oh...
But you know what?
If we find Joe...
What if we really jumped to a parallel universe?
What are you going to do?
That would be fun!
It sure would.
It would be so much fun!
I wonder where Joe is... in the first place.
Upstairs?
Up there? He's definitely at the bottom.
No, not up there.
I mean, you know, out in the field.
It's like... it's like... it's like... it's like getting closer.
Yes, because of the pretty flowers.
That's true.
It could be anywhere.
I wonder...
It looks like a good place.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
When did I fall asleep?
When I woke up, I was back in my own world.
But I'm sure that world wasn't a dream.
I just want to go back to that world one more time.
I think I remember a butterfly flew in and switched places with me.
Butterflies... where are the butterflies?
Oh, I found them!
Oh, I found it!
Wait, wait, wait! You're an idol now, aren't you? I knew it!
Is this real? Really?
Eve, Saho, Ailee, and Miya are all here.
And I have my memories, so does that mean we're in a parallel universe?
That's awesome! Oh, my God! We can have a little more fun!
What?
You're probably not going to believe this, but...
I'm from a parallel universe.
Parallel universe? That's what they all say.
What? You look at me like that! No, I'm serious!
Really?
You know that band, The End of the Crown? Guys.
End of the Crown?
Yeah, there's a band called The End of the Crown, and they have everybody.
Same faces?
Yeah, five guys called Clownpop.
That's why I flew here.
Yeah, they flew in here.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! That's amazing!
I'm 23 years old.
I'm 23!
That's amazing!
How did you get here?
Butterflies hooted and hooted like this.
I was surrounded by white light.
And I was dancing so hard.
Was it before your song?
That's right! And here you are.
Oh!
That's great!
That's what I'm talking about! That's what I'm talking about!
Oh!
Once you don't mind.
I've got one in me.
The one and only
A pure heart
I followed your eyes.I followed your eyes
Into the truth
Rather than let it out
I won't share anything
I'm going for today
The two of us
I want to dream
This world
Here
If it's with you
Droll, droll, dling, dling, dling, dling, dling.
I hope you all enjoyed my story.
Are you sure this wasn't all a dream?
I guess parallel universes do exist.
Well, this world is full of incredible things.
Maybe next time it'll come to you.
Aren't we all missing something?
We're missing something.
Yeah, I know.
I'm missing something, I'm missing something, I'm missing something, I'm missing something.
Not enough, not enough, not enough.
But it was a great movie, wasn't it?
It was a great movie, wasn't it?
It was great.
I couldn't stop watching it.
It was too good.
Hey, guys... now that we're here...
Don't you guys want to celebrate better?
Make sure...
Be sure.
Will you sing Happy Birthday to me?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, ready? Here we go.
Ready?
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday
Let's live on, Staykuyuu
Happy Birthday
image
leave
Thank you very much.
When?
Now.
I don't know, it just never ends,
What am I doing?
I know, right?
Oh, man.
I really wanted to sing with you guys.
Oh, yeah.
It's like, once and for all, we're not doing the nativity concert,
He just said surprise.
It's a surprise now.
Thank you.
[Applause.
I just thought I made a live show today where I couldn't say congratulations to everyone.
[Laughter
I'm really sorry about that.
I got to do a lot of the things I wanted to do myself.
That was lovely.
Thank you so much.
Subtitle created by Miku Hatsune
Thank you for watching!
It was just a moment. I still remember it.
A puddle of water
The sky was so blue I cried
Birds singing, ears closed
Wearing the view of the window
South wind harmony
Endless dreams and
and the horizon that continues to shine
I wish I could go on like this
I wish I could go on forever
Muttering, shouting
I want to come and get you now
Words and music by Miho Nakajima
Song by Hatsune Miku
Video by Miku Hatsune